<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food Restaurant</string>
    <string name="birynai">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tA world-renowned Indian dish, biryani takes time and practice to make but is worth every bit of the effort. Long-grained rice (like basmati) flavored with exotic spices such as saffron is layered with lamb, chicken, fish, or vegetables cooked in a thick gravy. The dish is then covered, its lid sealed on with dough and the biryani is cooked on a low flame. This is definitely a special occasion dish.</string>
    <string name="chapati">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tChapati or Chapatti,  is a type of Indian flat bread popular among northern parts of India. This is a simple roti made with Whole wheat flour, salt, oil and water. Making them real soft is the tricky part and search engines just overflow with tips. As far as my verdict goes “eat them immediately after making”, having them hot off the griddle is the only solution to have them soft.  Ofcourse you can always store, reheat and eat, but they tend to become little chewy.</string>
    <string name="dosa">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tA dosa is South Indian, fermented crepe made from rice batter and black lentils. Masala Dosa, specifically, is when you stuff it with a lightly cooked filling of potatoes, fried onions and spices.</string>
    <string name="dumplings">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tDumpling is a broad classification for a dish that consists of pieces of dough (made from a variety of starch sources) wrapped around a filling or of dough with no filling. The dough can be based on bread, flour, or potatoes, and may be filled with meat, fish, cheese, vegetables, fruits, or sweets. Dumplings may be prepared using a variety of methods, including baking, boiling, frying, simmering, or steaming, and are found in many world cuisines. </string>
    <string name="friedmashi">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tShaanxi Pasta (mashi or cat\'s ear noodles), a kind of pasta favored by northwestern Chinese, can be either braised (like Braised Shaanxi Pasta) or stir-fried.It\'s rare to eat it at the local people's home especially at the youth's nowadays, since the way of making Shaanxi Pasta does need skills.  Hereunder is the most popular way to make Stir-fried Shaanxi Pasta.</string>
    <string name="marghertiapizza">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tPizza Margherita is a typical Neapolitan pizza, made with San Marzano tomatoes, mozzarella fior di latte,[1] fresh basil, salt and extra-virgin olive oil. </string>
    <string name="panzanella">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tPanzanella [pantsaˈnɛlla] or panmolle [pamˈmɔlle] is a Tuscan chopped salad of bread and tomatoes that is popular in the summer. It includes chunks of soaked stale bread and tomatoes, sometimes also onions and basil, dressed with olive oil and vinegar.</string>
    <string name="pasta">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tPasta (Italian pronunciation: [ˈpasta]) is a staple food[1] of traditional Italian cuisine, with the first reference dating to 1154 in Sicily. Also commonly used to refer to the variety dishes made with it, pasta is typically made from an unleavened dough of a durum wheat flour mixed with water or eggs, and formed into sheets or various shapes, then cooked by boiling or baking. Some pastas can be made using rice flour in place of wheat flour to yield a different taste and texture, or for those who need to avoid products containing gluten.</string>
    <string name="spinachnoodles">\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\tThese green spinach noodles have a very interesting texture and flavor--but they taste better than store-bought noodles because they're fresh. Use in soups, or serve alone; they are great either way</string>
</resources>
